

SKILLS

Pro Skills

HTML CSS SASS GIT Photoshop Premiere MS Office



CONTACT

- ★ 25 Goater Way, Fair Oak, SO50 7HT
- **** 07950299503
- ✓ despaul13@googlemail.com

PAUL WILLIAMS

PROFILE

For the past year I've been learning software development with the aim to be a full time software developer and excel in both the front and back end.

I have passed a course run by "Brad Traversy" of Traversy Media and currently in the process of completing a Javascript 2021 guide with "Maximilian Schwarzmuller".

With over a decade experience in touring the world, I am a hard-working and highly motivated individual who is experienced in both managing live events and assisting as crew.

I have excellent communication skills and a positive attitude which has helped in achieving many targets. Depending on the event this could vary from production work, liaising with artists/management and venue staff to ensure an event runs smoothly and successfully.

EXPERIENCE

SEPT 2020 - Present

Intraguard Ltd.

HM Court & Tribunal Officer, Winchester As a current SIA door supervisor with further training to HMCTS standard. My duty is to ensure the safety of all court staff and court users. With thorough checks, patrols and customer service.

JULY 2019 -Present

AP Security Ltd.

SIA Door Supervisor, National, UK
Working within the events industry to ensure
the safety of the event itself and all persons
involved. Notable events I worked; Royal Albert
Hall, UK's First Biosecure venue for the
international cricket following the CV19
Pandemic.

MAY 2014 -JUNE 2019

REP5 Ltd.

Company Director, Southampton
Running my own company taught me a variety
of different buisness skills from financial
reports to people management. Where i
worked primarily within the live music industry
this included equipment hire, van hire, repping
for international promoters and in house venue
events. For these types of events i gained
experiance using Photoshop and Mailchimp for
email marketing.

EDUCATION



CONTACT

- ★ 25 Goater Way, Fair Oak, SO50 7HT
- **** 07950299503
- ✓ despaul13@googlemail.com